fsastore.com 2018-08-22

# Privacy Policy

Last updated on May 3, 2018

This privacy policy describes how FSA Store Inc. ("FSA Store") collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: fsastore.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

### Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect some or all of the following personal information from you:

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password
  * Health or Medical Information such as prescription information
  * Searches you perform on our Web site
  * Names and email addresses provided if you opt into our "Refer a Friend" program
  * Content you post to our Web site, including without limitation, reviews, testimonials, and other feedback

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

We use this information to:

  * Fulfill your orders
  * Send you order confirmations
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer your account
  * Send you newsletters and mail
  * Contact you with offers
  * Send you more relevant marketing communications
  * Create a more personalized shopping experience on our Web site
  * Identify trends, conduct data analysis and determine the effectiveness of our marketing and promotions
  * Respond to your questions and concerns

### SMS Opt-In and Out

By providing your mobile phone number and deadline information, you hereby affirmatively consent to FSA Store’s use of your mobile phone number for calls and texts (including prerecorded and/or by automatic telephone dialing systems) in order to provide you with (i) reminder notifications regarding your account deadline; (ii) information and reminders regarding certain eligible product offerings and promotions; and (iii) any push notifications delivered by us. We will not assess any charges for calls or texts, but standard message charges or other charges from your wireless carrier may apply. Deadline information provided is based solely on your input; we cannot confirm the validity of the information provided. You may opt-out of receiving text messages from us by texting “STOP” in response to any texts. You may opt-out of receiving calls from us by stating that you no longer wish to receive calls during any call with us, or by emailing opt-out-calls@fsastore.com and specifying you want to opt-out of calls. You understand that we may send you a text confirming any opt-out by you.

### Choice/Opt-Out

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter, marketing emails or other communications by following the instructions included in these communications or you can access your account at My Account, located here. 

### Children

You must be 18 years of age or older to order products from FSA Store. We are committed to protecting the privacy and rights of children online. To that end, we do not collect any personally identifiable information from users who we know are under the age of 13. Should we discover or be informed that a child has submitted his/her or another child's personal information, we will delete such information.

### Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as processing credit card or debit card payments, fulfilling and shipping your order, analyzing usage data, providing marketing services or providing customer service. Additionally, third party providers may send promotional e-mails on our behalf or present advertisements on our behalf, a function called "behavioral targeted advertising." These providers may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies (i) to present advertisements tailored to interests you have shown while browsing, (ii) to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before so as to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements, and (iii) to understand the patterns of people who see advertisements. These companies are authorized to use your personal information _only as necessary_ to provide these services to us. If you wish to not have your personal information used to deliver targeted personalized advertising, you may opt-out of some companies' personalized advertising services by visiting <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>. 

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, or
  * if FSA Store is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored as text files by your Internet browser on your computer's hard drive. Most Internet browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to refuse cookies from Web sites or to remove cookies from your hard drive, but if you do, you may not be able to access or use portions of our Web site. We have to use cookies to enable you to select products, place them in an online shopping cart, and to purchase those products. If you do this, we keep a record of your browsing activity and purchase. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of activities that occur under your usage of the Web site, including products stored in your cart.

We may use another company to place cookies on your computer to collect non-personally identifiable information to compile aggregated statistics for us about visitors to our Web site.

#### Web beacons

Our Web site's web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our Web site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.

We use third parties to gather information about how you and others use our Web site. For example, we will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our Web site is used.

#### Links to Other Web Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of FSA Store. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit, as it may differ substantially from that of this privacy statement. FSA Store makes no representations or warranties nor is FSA Store responsible for the privacy policies of any third party. If you decide to access any third party links appearing on the Site, you do so at your own risk.

Our Site includes in particular a hyperlink to https://phil.us/ (the “Phil Site”), a pharmacy prescription fulfillment website owned and operated by Phil, Inc. The FSA Store terms and conditions and this privacy statement do not extend to the Phil Site and we therefore encourage you to review the Phil Site terms and conditions and privacy policy before accessing, using or providing any information to the Phil Site. Any personal information, including prescription and credit card information, that you provide via the Phil Site, will be governed by the Phil, Inc. terms and conditions and privacy policy. FSA Store does not receive or access any personal or health information that you may provide to Phil, Inc. via the Phil Site and Phil, Inc. is prohibited from sharing your information with FSA Store.

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [privacy@fsastore.com](mailto:privacy@fsastore.com)

### Additional Policy Information

#### Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information

To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, access your account at My Account, located here. 

#### Notification of Privacy Policy Changes

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Web site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

#### Your California Privacy Rights

Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, California customers are entitled to request information relating to whether a business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. As explained elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, FSA Store will not sell or transfer your personal information to third party companies for their direct marketing purposes without your consent. California customers who wish to request further information about our compliance with this statute or who have questions more generally about our Privacy Policy and our privacy commitments to our customers and Web site users should not hesitate to contact us at the address or phone number below.

### Contact Information

You can contact us about this privacy policy by writing or email us at the address below:

FSA Store Inc.   
240 w 37th St 6th Floor   
New York, NY, United States 10018 

Email:
Phone:
